[{"answer": "The Queen went over to Kensington Palace this morning, primarily to meet her first great grandson, but I think William, he runs everything by her when it comes to the monarchy and how he does things and matters of state.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "I -- is there anything that goes on where there are some type of informal protocol with the queen where ahead of time they kind of run names by her, or is she finding out about it like anybody else's?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Right now, certainly it is.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "I may be -- I'm not saying great either way, but is that really happening?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "I think it's problematic for both of these candidacies in part because while we have turned this election into a -- sort of a two-ring circus, the bottom line is when you go out and campaign and talk to voters, working people, middle class people, they want to know about affordable housing, they want to know about education opportunities for their kids.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "Is there any chance at this point Weiner gets elected?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "No, Donny, I'm not getting paid at all and I'm not even sure that's her real name.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "Nik, first of all, are you getting paid by Miss Leathers?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "No, she submitted a tip to the site.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "What was the reason she came to you?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "Well, what happened was that she actually e-mailed Weiner in 2011 and it wasn't a nice e-mail.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Was that true?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Well, Donny, to me, I look at the Internet and I say, you know, privacy is gone.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "So what are -- just as a member of the 300 million people of this country say to yourself before you put something like this out ?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "I don't see him coming back from it, and Donny, you know, a lot of people -- we've been talking about whether or not he can win.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "Any chance?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "First of all, my disclosure is that I know Huma Abedin very well.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "He comes in your office, what do we do now?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Actually it was feminism period.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "As a woman when you're watching Huma, was that feminism at the high point or low point?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "There is no way Anthony Weiner would be in this race if Huma hadn't sign on at the beginning.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Is that your take?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "I just don't buy it.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "Marc, obviously, any woman could -- you're not buying it?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "At this point, what we're dealing with is sort of the personal because it's a sexual issue and the professional.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "How does anybody look past this?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Look, I love Hillary Clinton as one of my best friends and this obviously is a painful experience for her, because I know she loves Huma Abedin as those of us who know Huma do.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "If she's in the line next to Hillary, this will not go away and Hillary has a history of when there is a deficit she walks away?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "I did not send it to that woman in Washington State.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "You didn't send that photo to that woman in Washington State?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "I'll say we're doing everything we can to answer that question, but we're doing an investigation.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "But you're not 100 percent sure whether the photo is actually you?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "Well, I -- I think that for a lot of men who are either celebrities because they are in the entertainment business or sports world or because they are well-known elected officials or politicians or hope to be politicians, that they cheat frankly often because they don't believe that there will be consequences that will be serious, that they have the opportunity to do it and because frankly, they have not had to suffer serious consequences in the past.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "But isn't a lot of it just the opportunity?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "This is a little bit of a master of the universe mentality.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "Is there any thread that you've seen in men over the years -- powerful men, beyond kind the obvious sense of entitlement that causes this behavior?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "ONAGHUE: No, I'm going to agree with you.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "I mean, so what is sex addiction?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "I don't think people in their 20s are going to be like -- just think that anything that takes place on the internet is weird certainly.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "And then there's new digital generation -- are they going to look at this a lot with a lot kinder eyes than we would because they're growing up in the digital world and there's a lot more cavalierness to what happens in that virtual world?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "Arrogance will keep him in.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Star, Weiner have any chance?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Well, Donnie, I think the question is whether you acted on that.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Ben?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Can you profile and follow our children while they walk home and not do anything illegal?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "They -- they come to terms with the fact that the assumption is racist.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "...but like what do we -- how do we get past it (ph)?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "Well, they're trying to take something painful and negative and turn it into a positive.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "How are they doing?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "I just think that diversity around the table is what's going to move the conversation from talking to action.", "docId": "130724pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "Star, last word?", "qSentId": 668}]